[META] timeline_id=elder_care_day_v2 mode=rtsp24h slots=5760 events=169 clip_seconds=15 slots_sha1=4248a4a813debbd58594a0301f1c838cc4dc0513 generated=2026-08-21T16:00:25
#0000 [NIGHT] Elder tossing and turning repeatedly in bed, unable to settle
#0320 [NIGHT] Elder sitting up on the bed edge at night, motionless and dazed
#0520 [NIGHT] Elder tossing and turning repeatedly in bed, unable to settle
#0600 [NIGHT] Elder sitting up on the bed edge at night, motionless and dazed
#0680 [NIGHT] Elder out of bed at night, lamp on, pacing inside the room
#0760 [NIGHT] Elder getting out of bed and leaving the room at night
#0840 [NIGHT] Elder returning to the room and lying back down in bed
#0920 [STAFF] Care worker entering the room at night for a check, then leaving
#1452 [WAKE] Elder getting up in the morning and opening the curtain
#1476 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#1500 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1524 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#1548 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1572 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#1596 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1620 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#1644 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#1668 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1692 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1716 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#1740 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#1764 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1788 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#1812 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#1836 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1860 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#1884 [STAFF] Care worker entering the room in daylight, then leaving
#1908 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#1932 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#1956 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#1980 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#2004 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2028 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2052 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#2076 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2100 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#2124 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2148 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2172 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2196 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2220 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#2244 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2268 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#2292 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2316 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2340 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#2364 [STAFF] Care worker entering the room in daylight, then leaving
#2388 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2412 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2436 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2460 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#2484 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2508 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2532 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#2556 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2580 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#2604 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2628 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2652 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2676 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2700 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2724 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2748 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2772 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2796 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2820 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#2844 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2868 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2892 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2916 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#2940 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#2964 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#2988 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#3012 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3036 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#3060 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3084 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#3108 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3132 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3156 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3180 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3204 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#3228 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3252 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3276 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3300 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3324 [REST] Elder lying on the bed taking an afternoon nap
#3348 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3372 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3396 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3420 [RESTLESS] Elder repeatedly sitting down and standing up, visibly restless
#3444 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3468 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3492 [RESTLESS] Elder repeatedly sitting down and standing up, visibly restless
#3516 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3540 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3564 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#3588 [RESTLESS] Elder repeatedly sitting down and standing up, visibly restless
#3612 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3636 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3660 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3684 [RESTLESS] Elder repeatedly sitting down and standing up, visibly restless
#3708 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3732 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3756 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#3780 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3804 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3828 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3852 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3876 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3900 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#3924 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#3948 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#3972 [STAFF] Care worker entering the room in daylight, then leaving
#3996 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4020 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4044 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4068 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4092 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4116 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4140 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4164 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4188 [STAFF] Care worker entering the room in daylight, then leaving
#4212 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4236 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4260 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4284 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4308 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4332 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4356 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4380 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4404 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4428 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4452 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#4476 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4500 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4524 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4548 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4572 [STAFF] Care worker entering the room in daylight, then leaving
#4596 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4620 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4644 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4668 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4692 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#4716 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4740 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4764 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4788 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4812 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4836 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4860 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4884 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#4908 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#4932 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#4956 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#4980 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#5004 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#5028 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#5052 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#5076 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#5100 [CALM] Elder sitting on the bed edge looking at a phone
#5124 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#5148 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#5172 [ACTIVITY] Elder pacing back and forth across the room
#5196 [CALM] Elder sitting quietly in the armchair reading a book
#5220 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#5244 [CALM] Elder sitting in the armchair watching television
#5268 [REST] Elder drawing the curtain, turning off the light and going to bed
#5440 [STAFF] Care worker entering the room at night for a check, then leaving